



Eliecer Sánchez Mora

Nationality: Venezuelan Date of birth: 05/08/1995 Gender: Male

Caree 1 Phone number: (+58) 4120503212

Email address: eliecer.sanchez47@gmail.com

№ Whatsapp Messenger: +584245962899

in LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/eliecer-sanchez-mora-22688a26a

Website: https://eliecersm-portfolio.netlify.app

• Home: 48 Kampanella Triq Is-Siegh Is-Swieqi Aparment, SWQ 3050 Swieqi (Malta)

ABOUT ME

I really love programming and technologies and i think i'm ready to be a part of a great team as a junior developer and give my best, i'm flexible and have a lot of energy to keep learning like everybody does when you got a purpose, work hard with passion and resposibly like all of things i've done in my life.

As a Fullstack developer, i prefer both frontend and backend, i realy like working with JavaScript (libraries, framework (Reactjs and Nodejs), and i keep learning everyday. based on my past experience into the programming world, i manage good logic and work under preassure, i'm creative and with a possitive mentality to resolve problems.

The most of times i have worked independendly, but i'd like to be a part of a work team and i know it would be nice for me and other based my communication skills in other jobs, friends and people in everywhere.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

University Technician in Computer Science

University Institute of Technology "Antonio José de Sucre" [15/09/2014 - 01/02/2019]

City: Barquisimeto **Country:** Venezuela

Website: http://www.utsbarquisimeto.edu.ve/

Programming Logic and Java SE level 1 course

CADIf1 [21/08/2016 - 26/10/2016]

City: Baquisimeto **Country:** Venezuela

Website: https://cadif1.com/

English Conversation 1 Course

Westminster [22/11/2017 - 22/03/2019]

City: Barquisimeto **Country:** Venezuela

Website: https://gelvez.com.ve/barquisimeto/idiomas/27625-idiomas-westminster.html

WORK EXPERIENCE

Reactjs and Nodejs developer

Autodidact [02/05/2022 - Current]

City: Barquisimeto **Country:** Venezuela

- Learning JS library React is and developing sofware, improving my skills with time and practice
- Learning Node js and building APIs REST for some of my developed sofwares made

JavaScript Student

Autodidact [02/01/2022 - 02/04/2022]

City: Barquisimeto **Country:** Venezuela

- Learning bases of JS and building some small sofwares and pages

Database suport and Administrator (MySQL)

Lara State Goberment [01/05/2018 - 31/08/2018]

City: Barquisimeto **Country:** Venezuela

- manage Database for worker assistance system
- ensure data integrity

Java SE developer

Lara State Goberment [01/05/2018 - 01/09/2018]

City: Barquisimeto **Country:** Venezuela

- Improve worker assintance system built in Java SE

Java SE developer

University Institute of Technology "Antonio José de Sucre" and then Freelancer [02/01/2019 – 31/12/2019]

City: Barquisimeto **Country:** Venezuela

- I have developed an Automated system for managing graduates of my university
- As freelacer i developed an Automated inventory system for a client

DIGITAL SKILLS

VisalStudio Code / Postman API / Mongo DB and PostgreSQL / Reactjs / Nodejs / Social Media / Tailwind CSS / Socket.io / Express js

APTITUDES

good communication, empathy and camaraderie

analytical skills and work under pressure

[Current]

ability to solve problems

willingness to learn and risk

having a good business sense

ability to handle criticism

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): **Spanish**

Other language(s):

English

LISTENING B2 READING B1 WRITING B2

SPOKEN PRODUCTION B2 SPOKEN INTERACTION B1

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user